Local 1199 Photograph Files 5933 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- March 1971 - Salute to Freedom - Awards (Box 27, Folder 6)
- March 1971 - Salute to Freedom - Performers (Box 27, Folder 7)
- March 1971 - Salute to Freedom (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Salute to Freedom 1973 -- Performances (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Salute to Freedom 1973 -- Speakers (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Salute to Freedom - 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Salute to Freedom 1974 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Salute to Freedom - 1974 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Salute to Freedom - March 1976 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- 1977 Salute to Freedom (Box 27, Folder 15)
- 1977 Salute to Freedom (Box 27, Folder 16)
- 1978 Salute to Freedom (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Salute to Freedom 1981 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Salute to Israel, April 1965 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- 1979 Save Brooklyn Jewish - Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Save Brooklyn Jewish 1979 - Speakers (Box 27, Folder 21)
- 1979 Save Brooklyn Jewish - Strikes and Rallies (1) (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Save Brooklyn Jewish 1979 - Strikes and Rallies (2) (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Save Brooklyn Jewish 1979 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Save our hospitals rally, City Hall - May 23, 1979 (1) (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Save our hospitals rally, City Hall - May 23, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Save our hospitals rally, 5/23/1979 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Save Syndenham Hosp. - Metropolitan Hosp. -- Feb.-Mar. 1980 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Scholarship 1978 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Scholarship 1978 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- School Integration (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Sculptor - Sam Media of Montifiore Hosp. -- April, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Sculptor - Sam Media of Montifiore Hosp. -- April, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- SEIU/1199 Conf. - June 4-6, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- SEIU/1199 Conf. - June 4-6, 1981 (2) (Box 28, Folder 8)
- SEIU/1199 Conf. - June 4-6, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- SEIU/1199 Conf. - June 4-6, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- SEIU/1199 Conf. -- June 4-6, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Sickle Cell Committee (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Sleep Study - Montifiore Hosp. (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Social Events (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Social Events (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Solidarity 1199 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Solidarity Day 1981 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Solidarity Day - Sept. 19, 1981 (1) (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Solidarity Day - Sept. 19, 1981 (2) (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Solidarity Day - Sept. 19, 1981 (3) (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Solidarity Day - Sept. 19, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Southampton Hospital Organization Drive - October 1966 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Southside Hospital Delegates in action (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Sown Seeds + Sweet Sauce (Box 28, Folder 24)
- 11/1970 -- Spanish Dance (Box 28, Folder 25)
- St. Barnabas -- LPNs-RNs -- 1982 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- St. Clare's Hospital (Box 28, Folder 27)
- 1973 St. Clare's Org. (Box 28, Folder 28)
- 1973 St. Clare's Org. - Building (Box 29, Folder 1)
- St. Clare technicals (Box 29, Folder 2)
- St. John's Hospital (Catholic) (Box 29, Folder 3)
- St. Luke's Org. Campaign -- 1973 (1) (Box 29, Folder 4)
- St. Luke's Org. Campaign 1973 (2) (Box 29, Folder 5)
- St. Luke's - Newburgh (Box 29, Folder 6)
- 1968 - St. Michaels Strike (1) (Box 29, Folder 7)
- 1968 - St. Michael's Strike (2) (Box 29, Folder 8)
- 1968 - St. Michael's Strike (3) (Box 29, Folder 9)
- St. Vincent's Hospital election - Dec. 1980 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- St. Vincent Hospital (Box 29, Folder 11)
- St. Vincent - 2/1988 (Sante Fe RN Strike) (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Street Fair - 1983 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- 1963 Strikes (Box 29, Folder 14)
- 50's Strike - Drug + Hospital (1) (Box 29, Folder 15)
- 50's Strike - Drug + Hospital (2) (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Dec. 1967 Strike (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Strike Staff (1) (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Strike Staff (2) (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Strikes - Miscellaneous - Hospitals (Box 29, Folder 20)
- 1959 Strikes - Mount Sinai (Box 29, Folder 21)
- 1959 Strikes (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Strikes (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Strikes, Demonstrations (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Strikes, Demonstrations (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Strikes, Demonstrations (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Strikes, Demonstrations (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Supermarket (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Supporting Other Unions (1) (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Supporting Other Unions (2) (Box 29, Folder 30)
- 1969 Suzie Murray - Guild Member (1) (Box 30, Folder 1)
- 1969 Suzie Murray - Guild Member (2) (Box 30, Folder 2)
- 1969 Suzie Murray - Guild Member (3) (Box 30, Folder 3)
- 1969 Suzie Murray - Guild Member (4) (Box 30, Folder 4)
- 1969 Suzie Murray - Guild Member (5) (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Syosset - 1980 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Syosset - 1980 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Syosset -- 1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  negatives 1-12
- Take time, Take care -- 1982 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Theater 1199 - Don Huntstein - 1965-66 -- Group Theatre - Workshop (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Theater 1199 -- Don Huntstein - 1965-66 -- Group Theatre - Workshop (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Theater 1199 - Don Huntstein photos -- 1965-66 -- Group Theater Workshop (2) (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Theater 1199 - Don Huntstein photos -- 1965-66 -- Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Theater 1199 - Don Huntstein photos -- 1965-66 -- 'Shakespeare scene by scene' (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Theater 1199 - 1970-71 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Trade Union Save (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Thomas, Norman -- died Dec. 19, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Training + Upgrading (Generic + Older Pics) (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Training Fund - 1st Grad of Med. School (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Unemployment (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Unidentified Slides (Box 30, Folder 21)
  22 slides
- Unidentified slides (Box 30, Folder 22)
  16 slides
- Union Women's Conf. -- 1/ 1974 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- United Hospitals - Newark 10/1975 -- Ossie Davie + Mrs. King (Box 30, Folder 24)
- University Hospital Strike Vote (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Upstate New York (Box 30, Folder 26)
- 1969 - Oct. - Vietnam Moratorium (1) (Box 30, Folder 27)
- 1969 - Oct. - Vietnam Moratorium (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Jan. 1970 -- Vietnam War Protest (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Voter Registration (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Voter Registration (2) (Box 30, Folder 31)
- 1968 Wage Campaign ($100/week) (1) (Box 30, Folder 32)
- 1968 Wage Campaign ($100/week) (2) (Box 30, Folder 33)
- 1968 Wage Campaign ($100/week) (3) (Box 30, Folder 34)
- 1968 Wage Campaign ($100/week) (4) (Box 30, Folder 35)
- 1968 Wage Campaign ($100/week) (5) (Box 30, Folder 36)
- 1968 Wage Campaign ($100/week) (6) (Box 31, Folder 1)
- 1968 Wage Campaign ($100/week) (7) (Box 31, Folder 2)
- July 1966 - Wage Campaign, Demonstrations -- victory meeting at Manhattan Center (Box 31, Folder 3)
- July 1966 Victory meeting at Manhattan Center (2) (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Wall St. Demonstration - S. Africa (Box 31, Folder 5)
- War (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Warsaw Ghetto Memorial -- 1967 Exhibits (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Warsaw Ghetto Memorial -- 1967 Exhibit - Visitor (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Warsaw Ghetto Memorial -- 1967 Exhibit -- Visitor (2) (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Washington - Vietnam War Protest - 1965 -- 11/15/1969 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Welfare Strikes Support (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Westchester (Box 31, Folder 12)
- W. Va. Public Employees Conf. -- 12/1982 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- W. Va., Public Employees Conf. -- 12/1982 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Westport + Southport Strikes (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Westport + Southport Strikes (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Wisconsin, Del. Assembly -- Oct. 31, 1986 - Nov. 1, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Woodhull (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Woodhull 1981 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Woodhull 1981 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Woodland Strike -- 9/22/1975 - 11/28/1975 (1) (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Woodland Strike 9/22/1975-11/28/1975 (2) (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Woodland Strike 9/22/1975 - 11/28/1975 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Woodland Strike 9/22/1975 - 11/28/1975 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- X-Ray Conference (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Yachnes - X-Mas -- 1970 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Connecticut - Includes New Haven and others (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Connecticut - Includes New Haven and others (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Connecticut - Includes New Haven and others (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Connecticut - Hartford (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Delaware - Includes Wilmington and others (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Illinois (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Indiana (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Indiana (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Indiana (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Indiana - Gary (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Iowa (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Kentucky (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Kentucky - Prestonsburg (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Kentucky - Prestonsburg (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Maine (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Maryland - Baltimore (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Massachusetts (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Massachusetts (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Massachusetts (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Massachusetts (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Massachusetts - Boston (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Massachusetts - Boston (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Massachusetts - Springfield (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Michigan (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Michigan (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Michigan - Detroit (Box 33, Folder 1)
- New Hampshire - Portsmouth (Box 33, Folder 2)
- New Mexico (Box 33, Folder 3)
- New Mexico (Box 33, Folder 4)
- New York (Box 33, Folder 5)
- New York - Rochester (Box 33, Folder 6)
- New York - Rochester (Box 33, Folder 7)
- New York - Rochester (Box 33, Folder 8)
- New York - Rochester (Box 33, Folder 9)
  32 photographs
- New York - Rochester (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Puerto Rico (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Pennsylvania - Harrisburg (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania - Philadelphia (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Pennsylvania - Pittsburgh (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Rhode Island (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Rhode Island - Women and Infant's Hospital (Box 33, Folder 17)
- South Carolina - Includes Birmingham, Durham, and others (Box 33, Folder 18)
- South Carolina - Charleston (Box 33, Folder 19)
- South Carolina - Columbia (Box 33, Folder 20)
- South Carolina (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Washington, D.C. (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Seattle, Wash. - RN's (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Wisconsin (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Wisconsin Health Professionals - Vote 1199 - Nov. 1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Wisconsin Health Professionals Vote 1199 - Nov. 1980 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Oct. 1985 - Wisconsin - Represen. Assoc. + Cuban Health Care (Box 34, Folder 7)
- 1199 - Annual Delegate Assembly - Aug. 1960 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Henry Nichols in N.Y. (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Ohio, W. Virginia (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Ohio, W. Virginia (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Disability Pensions + Social Security (Box 34, Folder 12)
- News Clips (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Jerry Brown Portraits (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Jerry Brown Portraits (Box 35, Folder 2)
  29 photographs
- Jerry Brown Portraits + Misc. (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Feature about members (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Feature about members (Box 35, Folder 5)
- National Union Officers (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Round Table - National Convention (Box 35, Folder 7)
- National Union - 1199 Northwest (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Eddy Brown + Gerry Brown - Puerto Rico -- 1981 [Miller] (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Rev. (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Curled photographs (Box 35, Folder 11)
- 1199 News -- March 1983 Issue (Box 35, Folder 12)
- 1199 News -- April Issue (Box 35, Folder 13)
- 1199 News April 1983 Issue (Box 35, Folder 14)
- 1199 News -- May 1983 Issue (Box 35, Folder 15)
- 1199 News -- May 1983 Issue (Box 35, Folder 16)
- 1199 News - June 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 1)
- 1199 News - June 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 2)
  15 photographs; 1 slide
- 1199 News - July 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 3)
- 1199 News - July 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 4)
- 1199 News - August 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 5)
- 1199 News - August 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 6)
- 1199 News - September 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 7)
- 1199 News - September 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 8)
- 1199 News - October 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 9)
- 1199 News - October 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 10)
- 1199 News - October 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 11)
- 1199 News - October 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 12)
- 1199 News - November 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 13)
- 1199 News - December 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 14)
- 1199 News - December 1983 Issue (Box 36, Folder 15)
- 1199 News - January 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 1)
- 1199 News - February 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 2)
- 1199 News - March 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 3)
- 1199 News - April 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 4)
- 1199 News - May 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 5)
- 1199 News - June-July 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 6)
- 1199 News August-September 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 7)
- 1199 News - October 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 8)
- 1199 News - November 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 9)
- 1199 News - November 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 10)
- 1199 News - November 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 11)
- 1199 News - December 1984 Issue (Box 37, Folder 12)
- 1199 News - January 1985 Issue (Box 37, Folder 13)
- 1199 News - January 1985 Issue (Box 37, Folder 14)
- 1199 News - February 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 1)
- 199 News - March 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 2)
- 1199 News - March 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 3)
  Contact Sheets
- 1199 News - April 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 4)
- 1199 News - June-July 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 5)
- 1199 News - May 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 6)
- 1199 News - May 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 7)
- 1199 News - August-September 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 8)
- 1199 News - October 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 9)
- 1199 News - November-December 1985 Issue (Box 38, Folder 10)
- 1199 News - January 1986 Issue - Unused Photos (Box 38, Folder 11)
- 1199 News - January 1986 Issue (Box 38, Folder 12)
- 1199 News - February 1986 Issue (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Home Care Workers Rally, C. O'Connor, Jesse Jackson, Eddy Kay, Andrew Stein, Phillip Randolph, Georgianna Johnson (Box 38, Folder 14)
  20 slides
- Home Care Workers Rally - Cardinal O'Connor (cont.) (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Home Care Rally (Box 38, Folder 16)
  10 slides
- Unlabeled slides (Box 38, Folder 17)
  21 slides
- Unlabeled (Box 38, Folder 18)
  5 slides; 5 photographs
- Russian visitors and Davis, 10/1971 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  #1505
- Emblem of National Union in color, 10/1975 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  #2162 -- 20 slides
- Emblem of National Union in color, 10/1975 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  #2162 -- 15 slides
- Unidentified Photographs - include strikes, meetings around Washington (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Early Drug Union - (1199 photos) (Box 38, Folder 23)
- 1199 News - March 1986 Issue - Photographs (Box 39, Folder 1)
- 1199 News - April 1986 Issue Photographs (Box 39, Folder 2)
- 1199 News - April 1986 Issue Photographs (cont.) (Box 39, Folder 3)
- 1199 News - May 1986 Issue (Box 39, Folder 4)
- 1199 News - June 1986 Issue (Box 39, Folder 5)
- 1199 News - June 1986 Issue (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Davis visited at home during heart attack recovery (Box 40, Folder 1)
  1963 or 1964 -- #80
- St. Barnabas Strike victory, Oct. 1964 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  #81
- Caso Drug Strike, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  #82
- Legislative activity for hospital rights (Box 40, Folder 4)
  #83
- Brooklyn Jewish demo in layoffs (Box 40, Folder 5)
  1961 or 1961 -- #84
- Minimum wage rally (for $1.50 hr.) advertised at Brooklyn Jewish, 1962, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  #85
- Bernie Katz (Box 40, Folder 7)
  #86
- Drug demo for contract at Waldorf-Astoria (Box 40, Folder 8)
  #87
- Beth Israel vote - victory-Newark, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  #88
- Kaufman Dome Retiree petition-filler (Box 40, Folder 10)
  #89
- Johnson, Lyndon - 1199 Supports, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  #90
- Drug Legislature Activity (Box 40, Folder 12)
  #91
- Picnic (Box 40, Folder 13)
  #92
- Wagner Rally with Dr. King, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  1961? - #93
- Manhattan Eye + Ear meeting at Manhattan Center. VanArsdale, Randolph (Box 40, Folder 15)
  #94
- Ella Fitzgerald + 1199 at Concert (Box 40, Folder 16)
  #95
- Garment Strike - 1199 March in Support of District 65, May/1965 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  #96
- Albany, March 1965 in support of Unemployment Insurance + other union goals, 3/1965 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  #97
- St. John's Episcopal demonstration, April, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  #98 -- 11 photographs
- Joe Tamber and Leon Davis at Union Office, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  #99
- Beth-El Strike, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  #100
- #100A (Box 40, Folder 22)
- #100B (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Spanish Class - 3/12/1963 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  #200
- Picnic at Heckscher State Park, Aug. 16, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  #300
- Models wear 1199 hats, Summer 1964 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  #301
- New Jersey Hospital, Organizing rally M.L. King + Bayard Rustin, Oct. 1964 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  #350
- Civilian Review board Campaign - 1199ers - meet with City Councilman Aldrich, Fall, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  #351
- O'Laughlin, Sophie - with V-P Mitchell, Celebrate receipt of her citizenship papers, Fall, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  #352
- Retiree's meet, Fall, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  #353
- Joint Diseases Hosp. - Demonstration for 1st, 1199 Contract - Sept.-Oct. 1964 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  #354
- Education for delegates of Guild Div., Fall 1964 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  #55
- Retirees meet as new area of 1199, Fall 1964 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  #356
- Drug training aid (MDTA), Contract signed by Drug Div. Glotzer, Fall 1964 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  #357
- Spanish Affairs Comm., Fall 1964 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  #358
- Education Program starts for Delegates (Hosp.), Fall 1964 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  #359
- Jewish Memorial, 1st Contract signed, Fall 1964 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  #360
- Drug Delegate Class, Fall 1964, Al Nash instructor (Box 40, Folder 38)
  #361
- Dance - Union wide, Winter 1964 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  #362
- Northfield Nursing Home Strike, N.J., December 1964 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  #363
- Kiddie X-mas Party, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  #364
- Pharmacy Campaign for representation on State Board Albany delegation, 1/19/1965 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  #365
- Pharmacy Representation Campaign, Jan. 1965 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  #365 (cont.)
- Guild - Theatre Party, Jan. 28, 1965 -- Alan Alda, The Owl and the Pussy Cat (Box 40, Folder 44)
  #366
- Welfare Workers Strike, Jan-Feb 1965 -- 1199 Support (Box 40, Folder 45)
  #367
- Drug Store Spanish Class, 1/1965 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  #368
- Pre-paid Drug Plans, 2/1965 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  #369
- Theatre 1199, First One, Feb. 7, 1965 with Ossie & Ruby (Box 40, Folder 48)
  #370
- Sandlebrook Nursing Home Negotiating Committee, Feb. 1965 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  #371
- Plotnich, Henry - Credit Union Director (Addressing Hosp. Div. Delegate Assembly), 2/1965 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  #372
- Drug Spanish Class, 2/1965 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  #373
- NALC - Brewery Workers, Settlement with city, Feb. 1965 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  #374
- Nursing Homes Nego. Committee -- Representing: Beth Abraham; Daughters of Jacob; Odd Fellows; Daughters of Israel, Feb. 1965 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  #375
- Retiree Sam Lipow birthday party of union, March 1965 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  #376
- Lawrence Hospital Strike - Support demonstration by 1199 + Civil Rights Groups, 3/1965 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  #377
- Lawrence Hospital Strikers at party given by Harold & Virginia Turner + John and Bonnie Richardson of Bronxville, NY, 3/1965 (Box 40, Folder 56)
- Lawrence Hospital Strike - Support Demonstration by 1199 + Civil Rights Groups, Also individual strikers, Jan.-Feb. 1965 (Box 40, Folder 57)
- Lawrence Hospital Strike, Jan-Feb 1965 (Box 40, Folder 58)
- Credit Union - Credit Committee with loan applicant, 3/1965 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  #378
- Hearing State Senate, George Glotzer testify on "Pep Pills", 3/29/1965 (Box 40, Folder 60)
  #379
- Spanish language class for Drug Workers, March 1965 (Box 40, Folder 61)
  #380
- Strike at A.J. Medical Supply - 1 worker shop in New Hyde Park, L.I., March-April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 62)
  #381
- Retirees at Hyde Park, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  #382 -- 1 photograph
- Visitor to 1199 - Student from Atlanta U., April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 64)
  #383
- Community Service Course by AFL-CIO attended by 1199 Staff members, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 65)
  #384
- Spanish Class for drug working graduates, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 66)
  #385
- Spanish language meeting in general union + P.R. Civil rights problems, Geneva-Valentine, Guest Speaker, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 67)
  #386
- Esther Brown - Staff member and singer, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 68)
  #387
- Delegate in Action, henry Perez of Franzer Drug, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 69)
  #388
- Freedom Democratic party supporters meet at 1199 - Rep. Wm. F. Ryan speaks, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 70)
  #389
- Delegate in action, Morton Rephen, Brooklyn Store, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 71)
  #390
- Brandywine Nursing Home Strike, April-May 1965 (Box 40, Folder 72)
  #391
- Brandywine Nursing Home Strike, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 73)
- Tauber, Joseph - His portrait in 1199's Tauber Room, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 74)
  #392
- Bayard Rustin speaks at 1199 forum, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  #393
- Delegates' Class - Drug 2 delegates and enact grievance session, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 76)
  #394
- Douglas, Frederick - Portrait in 1199's F. Douglass Room, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 77)
  #395
- Bloomingdale Strike - Support 1199, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 78)
  #396
- Instructor Training - Staff being trained to teach delegate classes, 3/1965, 4/1965 (Box 40, Folder 79)
  #397
- Trofalgan Hospital - Members meet at Union, 4/1965 (Box 40, Folder 80)
  #398
- Ramapo Manor Nursing Center, Rockland County, NY, 4/1965 (Box 40, Folder 81)
  #399
- Visitor from Jamaica, 4/1965 (Box 40, Folder 82)
  #400
- Hiring through the Union, Hospital Personnel Directors Confer. At Union, 4/1965 (Box 40, Folder 83)
  #401
- Wedding of Bill Little and Holly Baumann party at Union, 4/3/1965 (Box 40, Folder 84)
  #402
- Camp Scholarship Program - Drug kids being interviewed, 4/3/1965 (Box 40, Folder 85)
  #403
- Beth Abraham Home - Members ratify contract renewal, 4/1965 (Box 40, Folder 86)
  #404
- H.I.P. Washington Heights Center meets at Union, 4/2/1965 (Box 40, Folder 87)
  #405 - (1) 8x10 of neg. #28A-29
- Parker Anita of N.Y. Infirmary aspiring actors, April 1965 (Box 40, Folder 88)
  #406
- Credit Union Bank, 4/1965 (Box 40, Folder 89)
  #407
- Benefit Plan, Trustee Meeting, May 1965 - (Dr. Ralph Snyder) (Box 40, Folder 90)
  #408
- Delegate Assembly Hosp. Div., hears W. Va. Hosp. Striker, May 1965 -- Org. John Blach - Talks on Brandywine Strike (Box 40, Folder 91)
  #409
- Hiring Hall gets new job for Jaime Lee in Community Hosp., May 1965 (Box 40, Folder 92)
  #410
- Ed Ayash - Treas., Dick Logan - Ed. Dir., May 1965 (Box 40, Folder 93)
  #411
- Delegates graduate Univ. Training Course (Individual faces), May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  #412
- Jasper Brown of Drug Division - Shows Joe Meneses of Personal Service Dept., May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  #413
- Strike support to District 65, Garment Center Workers, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  #414
- Mildred Clark of Jewish Home for aged portrait, June 1965 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  #415
- Delegates enact grievance session at union class, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  #416
- Theatre 1199 - O'Casey Evening, May 16, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  #417
- Credit Union Passbook, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  #418
- Credit Union's - Joe Brenner, Chairman, Credit Union Comm., May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  #419
- Spanish Affairs Committee Dance, May 22, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  #420
- Negro American, Labor Council, Chapter induct. 1199ers to office, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  #421
- Hiring Hall, Members check job list, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  #422
- Clerical workers meeting (Hosp. Div.), May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  #423
- Lewis, John of Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee visits 1199, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  #424
- Negro American Labor Council Convention M.L. King/Bill Taylor Speakers, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  #425
- Montefiore Hosp., Research Technician, Harold Gorelick on the job, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  #426
- Montefiore Workers meet on the job with V.P. Ramirez, May 1965 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  #427